For boarding students at Bodwell, there is much more to consider
보드웰에서 보딩 프로그램에 참여하는 학생은
throughout the day than an average high school student
일반 고등학생보다 생각해야 할 것들이 많습니다
Students here are expected to responsibilities in all area their life
학생은 새로운 환경, 새로운 학교, 새로운 사람들에 적응함과 동시에
while adapting to a new environment, new school, and new people.
생활 모든 방면에서 책임감을 갖도록 요구됩니다
It can be very overwhelming.
당연히 벅찰 수가 있죠
For this reason, it is necessary to establish a routine that students can follow,
그렇기 때문에 학생이 따라갈 수 있는 루틴을 만들어서
to help them structure their day and develop the proper time management skills needed
학생이 하루 일정을 짜고 시간 관리 기술을 익히도록 하는 것이 중요합니다
to be successful in all areas of a boarding student's life
모든 방면에서 성공적인 보딩 생활을 위한 첫걸음으로
A student's day begins with the wake-up call at 7 a.m.
7시에 학생은 기상 소리와 함께 일어납니다
By 8:00, all the boarding areas are closed and students
8시면 기숙사의 모든 구역이 닫히게 되어
are not allowed to re-enter until the end of the academic day.
학생은 수업 시간동안 다시 기숙사에 들어올 수 없게 됩니다
We want students to develop the habit of bringing everything they need from their home to class
이는 학생이 수업 준비물을 항상 챙기도록 하는 습관을 길러줍니다
Breakfast is available from 7:25 to 8:15 every morning
학생은 매일 7시 25분에서 8시 15분 사이에 아침 식사를 합니다
Breakfast is an important meal and we encourage students to eat by extending meal time past boarding closure.
아침 식사는 중요하므로 기숙사가 닫힌 뒤로도 식사를 할 수 있도록 제공됩니다
At 3:30 p.m. The school day ends and clubs begin. These run from 3:30 to 4:30
오후 3시 30분이면 모든 수업이 끝나고 4시 30분까지 클럽 활동이 있습니다.
This is a great opportunity for students to work on
이때는 일주일에 한 번 또는 두 번씩
an extracurricular activity for once,  sometimes twice a week
학생이 방과후 활동에 참여할 수 있는 시간입니다
From 5:30 dinner is available for all boarding students.
5시 30분부터 보딩 프로그램 학생은 저녁 식사를 합니다
Our cafeteria stays open during supper for 45 minutes
카페테리아는 저녁 식사 45분 동안 열려있습니다
Study-hall begins at 6:00 with small group tutoring for those requiring extra help
6시부터 그룹 튜터를 추가 요청한 학생의 자습시간이 시작되고
At 7, Junior study all begins and at 8:15 we have senior study hall, where all senior students attend.
7시에는 주니어, 8시 15분부터는 모든 시니어 학생의 자습 시간이 시작됩니다
The library also remains open through the evening.
도서관 또한 저녁 내내 열려있습니다
Every Wednesday each individual Hall meets for announcements
매주 수요일 각각의 홀 학생은 모여서 있었던 일들을 얘기하며
and to discuss issues and further develop life skills and community building.
라이프 스킬 개발 및 커뮤니티 조성 시간을 갖습니다
Every hall meeting is run a little differently.
홀 미팅은 각각 다르게 운영되는데
It allows each hall to develop an individual sense of community within the boarding program.
이는 홀마다 보딩 프로그램 내에서 독자적인 커뮤니티를 형성하도록 합니다
After study hall snack is available in students of thirty minutes free time
자습 시간이 끝나면 자유 시간 30분 동안 간식이 제공되며
to begin heading back to their halls for curfew.
학생은 각자의 홀로 돌아가서 취침을 준비합니다
By 10:15 students are up in their boarding halls and begin their bedtime routines.
10시 15분이면 학생은 보딩 홀에서 취침 루틴을 행합니다
We give students an hour for their bedtime routine.
약 한 시간의 취침 루틴을 통해
This is a time for students to wash up,
학생은 세면을 하고 각자의 홀 커뮤니티 속에서
build a sense of community in their halls as well as relax and reflect before bed.
쉬거나 자기 전 하루를 돌아봅니다
We have a student that goes around to do the curfew check to-
학생중 자발적으로 인원 점검을 하려는 학생이 있으면
We give them some volunteer hours for that.
봉사 활동 시간을 부여합니다
And then later on the evening we'll go around again just to make sure that everybody is where they're supposed to be.
그러고 나서 밤늦게 학생이 각자 자리에 잘 있는지 한 번 더 점검을 합니다
At 11:00 all students are in their rooms followed by a lights out at 11:30
11시면 모든 학생은 자기 방에 있게 되고 11시 30분이면 불이 꺼집니다
Although the weekend schedule varies,
매주말에는 스케줄의 변동이 있지만
here in boarding we like to keep a structured weekday routine,
보딩 프로그램에서 주중 루틴은 일정하도록 유지되어
to allow students to focus on academics and further develop their life skills.
학생이 학업에 집중하고 라이프 스킬을 향상할 수 있도록 해줍니다